[{"question":"which object is smaller?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The porcelain cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"What is the material of the small cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"Porcelain"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"Bamboo"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has larger density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large bamboo cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Is the medium wood cube heavier than the large bamboo cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has lower friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large bamboo cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has lower restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium wood cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the small porcelain cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which quadrant will the large bamboo cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium wood cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small porcelain cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large bamboo cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the small porcelain cube travel to quadrant \u2161?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2161?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium wood cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the small porcelain cube collide with the large bamboo cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the medium wood cube collide with the large bamboo cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small porcelain cube and the large bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small porcelain cube and the medium wood cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The wall and the small porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The large bamboo cube and the medium wood cube"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large bamboo cube and the medium wood cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The wall and the large bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The medium wood cube and the small porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The small porcelain cube and the wall"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Will the medium wood cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1}]